export const QuizData = [
    {
        question: "The Full form of CSS is",
        options: ["coloured Special Sheets", "color and Style Sheet", "Cascading Style Sheets", "Cool Style Sheet"],
        ans: 3
    }, 
    {
        question: "How can We change the background color of n element?",
        options: ["background-color", "color", "Both A and B", "None of The Above"],
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "How can we change the text color of an element?",
        options: ["background-color", "color", "Both A and B", "None of The Above"],
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        question: "In How many ways can CSS be written in ?",
        options: ["3", "2", "1", "4"],
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "Which HTML tag is used to declare internal CSS?",
        options: ["<style>", "<link>", "<script>", "None of the above"],
        ans: 1
    },
    {
        question: "The CSS property used to specify the transparency of an element is?",
        options: ["visibility", "opacity", "filter", "None of the above"],
        ans: 2
    },
    {
        question: "How can we specify the spacing between each letter in a text in CSS?",
        options: ["alpha-spacing", "character-spacing", "letter-spacing", "None of the above"],
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        question: "Which of the following are valid ways to represent a colour in CSS?",
        options: ["A valid color name", "RGB values", "HEX values", "All of the above"],
        ans: 4
    },
    {
        question: "We can make rounded borders around elements using which CSS element",
        options: ["border-collaps", "border-round ", "border-radius", "None of the above"],
        ans: 3
    },
    {
        question: "How can we add more importance to a property/value than normal?",
        options: ["!important", "important", "bold", "None of the above"],
        ans: 3
    },
];